

About Me

Have experience in functional testing web applications and banking program. Familiar with APIs and Databases. Understanding of QA processes, testing types and approaches, requirements, methodology, etc. Creating test documentation (requirements, test cases, check-lists, bug reports, test reports). Have good communication skills and am a very responsible, attentive, dependable, sufficiently flexible, positive person.

Technical skills

- Technical Documentation/SRS
- TestRail
- Jira
- Azure DevOps
- JSON
- Rest API
- Fiddler Everywhere
- Postman
- Apache JMeter
- MySQL
- DevTools
- XML
- HTML/CSS
- XPath
- Selenium IDE
- Git
- SourceTree
- KDiff3

Languages

English - Intermediate

TETIANA MNOHOLITNIA

QA Engineer

- **L** +380661055339
- Dnipro, Ukraine
- mnogoletka8483@gmail.com
 https://www.linkedin.com/in/tetiana-mnoholitnia-249711340/
 https://github.com/Mnogoletka/Portfolio_QA_TetianaMnoholitnia

Work experience

Content manager/SEO specialist NDA, Ukraine

2019 - 2022

- Manual functional testing of web applications
- Filling websites with text and graphic information
- Drafting technical specifications for copywriters
- Internal SEO optimization (compilation of a semantic core, website structure development, filling in page meta tags, performing page interlinking)
- External SEO optimization (competitor analysis, link profile building: search for suitable donor sites and regular posting of articles)

Deputy Head of the Banking Operations Control Department

2006 - 2019

PUBLIC JOINT STOCK COMPANY «BANK VOSTOK», Ukraine

- Control and accounting of banking operations (loans, deposits of individuals and legal entities, interbank transactions, guarantees, factoring, securities)
- Checking bank statistical reporting files
- Preparation of settlements for problem debts
- Development and testing of requirements for automation of processing and control of transactions in the banking program

Education

QA Engineer

Sep 2024 - Dec 2024

Mentor Natalia Popelyshko (Senior Test Automation)

Practical Quality Assurance Course (test documentation, levels, types, test design techniques, API, SQL, Git)

Theoretical Software Testing Course

Finance Specialist

2001 - 2006

Dnipropetrovsk State Financial Academy